buffalowildwings.com 2019-06-29

# Privacy Policy Terms | Buffalo Wild Wings

Buffalo Wild Wings, Inc., its franchisees, marketing agencies, and affiliated contractors, as specifically identified here (collectively “BWW,” "we" or “us”), appreciate your patronage and take your privacy very seriously. As a result, we’ve developed the following policy terms which apply to all websites and mobile applications owned and operated by BWW, specifically including the buffalowildwings.com site and the Fight4Fandom Mobile App (collectively the “Site(s)”).

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand what personal information we may collect from you through our Sites, how we may use or share this information, and what steps you may take to control such use or sharing.

### What We Collect

We collect the information you affirmatively choose to provide us, such as when you provide your name, contact information, the pages you access and similar information for such purposes as purchasing products, creating an account, joining our loyalty programs, filling out a survey, entering contests, participating in promotions or electronic activities, posting comments on bulletin boards or otherwise interacting with our Sites. By accessing the Sites, you consent to receive materials and understand and acknowledge that you may receive emails and other communications from BWW. When you purchase a product from our Sites, we ask you to provide information to fulfill your order, including your name, email address, phone, shipping address, billing address and method of payment to facilitate your purchase. If you create an account through one of our Sites, this personal information will be stored by us. If you purchase products as a Site Guest, we will not store the personally identifiable information you provide.

We also collect your information through the use of cookies. Cookies are pieces of data your web browser stores on your hard drive to allow our Sites to provide you with enhanced services. Cookies allow us to store products in your online shopping cart, process orders, and recognize whether or not you have visited our Sites before. This provides us with important marketing information and lets us know how we are doing at both attracting new visitors and maintaining relationships with our existing customers.

If you wish, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. However, keep in mind that cookies are required to place an online order and for other user-friendly Site functions, so blocking cookies will negatively impact your Site experience. Should you wish to block cookies through your web browser, you may still purchase products through our Customer Service Department at 1-800-499-9586.

In some cases, we may also collect information from third-party sources, including social media sites and other sites with which we may partner on BWW branded promotions. For example, if you post a comment on our Facebook page or send us a message on Twitter, we may collect and use that information as described in this Privacy Policy. Please note that we may combine this information with other information that we collect about you and use it as described herein.

### **What We Do With What We Collect**

We use the personal information we collect for various purposes, including to complete a purchase that you initiate, to respond to your requests for information, to manage our Sites, to allow you to participate in electronic activities, marketing analysis, marketing communications, facilitating loyalty programs, and for other lawful purposes. From time to time, we may also contact customers by email, phone or mail for such purposes as to inform them of new products, services and special offers, administer a survey, or to follow up on previous interactions. If you do not wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the opt-out instructions generally provided in such communications. Upon your request, we will make reasonable efforts to delete your personal information from our database, however, it may be impossible to delete your entry without retaining some residual information for a period of time due to backups and records of deletion. Be assured that we will never knowingly send messages to customers who have asked not to receive them.

Any information you share with us pursuant to signing up for Buffalo Circle® or for any other purpose, will be shared as needed to facilitate that purpose. We generally do not share your information with companies who are not affiliated with us, but if we do, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of these communications at any time by contacting us at Buffalo Wild Wings, 5500 Wayzata Blvd, 16th Floor, Minneapolis, MN 55416, Attn: Marketing Department or by using the opt-out instructions in the communications themselves. Should you have questions about how we use your information, feel free to send us a message by visiting the Contact Us section of any of our Sites. Alternatively, you can contact us at 1-800-499-9586, and speak with a Customer Service representative.

We will not sell or rent the personally identifiable information you provide to us to any third party, except as stated herein. We may share your information within the BWW organization and with our franchisees, with current and future affiliated companies, and with reputable third parties as needed to provide better services to you. These third party services may include such tasks as maintaining and managing customer information, providing customer services, taking and fulfilling orders, conducting BWW promotions and surveys, and communicating effectively with you. We do not authorize those third parties to make any other use of your information unless indicated herein, and we will hold them accountable if it is discovered they use your information for any unauthorized purpose.

We may also disclose your personal information to third parties if we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with law, regulation, legal process or government request; enforce the terms of any of our policies; or protect the rights, property or safety of BWW, our associates, or our customers. This may include assistance in fraud protection and investigation. In addition, we may share or transfer your information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as a merger, consolidation, asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

### Links and Third-Party Content

Our Sites may contain links to other websites, which are not under our control. We provide these links as a customer convenience and to allow advertisers to promote their own sites or products, and do not endorse those sites, companies or their products or services. Also, when you link to our Sites from another site, the originating site may collect information about you. We do not review, control or monitor the practices, information or materials on any other websites, and are not responsible or liable for the communications, practices, information, content or materials from any of those sites. You are responsible for understanding and adhering to any other website's terms and conditions.

### Secure Online Ordering

For your security, we only store your credit card information if you choose to set up an authorized account with one of our Sites. In that case, it is stored on a secure computer in an encrypted format. If you do not set up an account, you will have to enter your credit card information each time you order. We understand that this may be a little inconvenient for you, but some customers appreciate the added security.

When you do place an order, your address and credit card information is transmitted using industry standard encryption technology called secure socket layers (SSL) which ensures that it is encrypted during transmission. The integrity of our safe shopping technology is verified by Verisign, the premier secure transaction accreditation authority. You will see the Verisign logo during the checkout process to confirm that you are in 'secure mode.' Additional security assurances are given by the locked padlock icon or solid key icon at the bottom of your browser window, and the letters "https" (rather than "http") located in the URL address window at the top of your browser.

### **Children's Privacy**

We are very concerned about protecting the safety and privacy of children. Our Sites are not intended for children. We do not specifically collect information about children and do not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18, get your parent's consent before giving out any personal information online.

### California Privacy Rights

Residents of the State of California may request a list of all third parties to which BWW has disclosed personal information during the preceding year for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and want such a list, you must send a request to:

_Buffalo Wild Wings  _  
 _Attn: Legal Department_  
 _5500 Wayzata Blvd, Suite 1600_  
 _Minneapolis, MN 55416_

You must provide the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in the subject field of your e-mail or on the envelope or post card and in the actual request. For all requests, please include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. We will not accept requests via the telephone or by fax. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.

### Privacy Policy Changes

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such amendments to this Policy may apply to information we collect in the future as well as any information we obtained from you prior to such amendment. We will post all changes to this Policy on the Sites, and we encourage all visitors and users of the Sites to check this policy from time to time.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: July 23, 2012.

Overview of Changes from Previous Policy: We added clarification regarding the use of collected information, consolidated all BWW privacy policies into one, and revised the Policy to comply with California law.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

_Buffalo Wild Wings  _  
 _Attn: Legal Department  _  
 _5500 Wayzata Blvd, Suite 1600  _  
 _Minneapolis, MN 55416_
